import { Quiz } from '../../types';

const BuildQuiz: Quiz[] = [
  {
    description: 'Jak to popisujeme?',
    name: 'Popis styl',
    questions: [
      {
        answer: ['casual'],
        question: 'casual'
      },
      {
        answer: ['trendy'],
        question: 'trendy'
      },
      {
        answer: ['classic'],
        question: 'klasický'
      },
      {
        answer: ['elegant'],
        question: 'společenský'
      },
      {
        answer: ['sporty'],
        question: 'sportovní'
      },
      {
        answer: ['bohemian'],
        question: 'bohémský'
      },
      {
        answer: ['hipster'],
        question: 'hipsterský'
      },
      {
        answer: ['feminine', 'lady like'],
        question: 'ženský'
      },
      {
        answer: ['casual'],
        question: 'pohodlný'
      },
      {
        answer: ['tomboy'],
        question: 'klučičí'
      },
      {
        answer: ['minimalist'],
        question: 'minimalistický'
      },
      {
        answer: ['professional'],
        question: 'profesionální'
      },
      {
        answer: ['romantic'],
        question: 'romantický'
      }
    ]
  }
];

export default BuildQuiz;
